palaceresorts.com 2013-06-07

# Privacy Policy | Palace Resorts | Mexico

## Privacy Policy

Personal Data collected from the User (name, home address, nationality, invoice address, credit/debit card numbers, age, gender, etc.) is limited to the purposes provided in the WEB SITE; this is for the execution and compliance of the services provided by PALACE RESORTS or any third parties requested by the User. The User hereby grants full consent to PALACE RESORTS for the collection, use, transfer and storage of the personal data including financial information provided by the User and for the transfer of such data to any third parties. Details of your travel arrangements or personal information shall not be revealed to any outside party except as necessary to process their reservations and travel arrangements. Such information may be transferred between Palace Resorts and its affiliates and subsidiaries, wherever located, for the compliance of the purposes detailed in the corresponding agreement.

For a User to file a formal written request of access, rectification, opposition and cancellation or any other limitation of the use of personal data please contact the phone and address provided below.

Such request shall be answered within 20 days. PALACE RESORTS may answer in a positive or negative manner as PALACE RESORTS considers applicable and according to Law. If the request is legitimate it shall be complied within 15 days after PALACE RESORTS issues an answer. Both terms may be doubled by PALACE RESORTS if necessary, as the case may be. The request shall only be received, answered and complied with by PALACE RESORTS if it is made according to law. All the costs and expenses incurred by such request shall be paid by User.

The use and disclosure of personal data is limited to legal, administrative or judicial provisions. Therefore if PALACE RESORTS uses data in any other manner than described herein in compliance with any legal, administrative or judicial provision it shall not be considered as a breach or infringement of this Terms of Use and Privacy Policy Notice. The consent granted in this agreement shall only be repealed by the procedure provided in the previous paragraph.

PALACE RESORTS does not abide by this privacy policy, please email us at [webmaster@palaceresorts.com](mailto:webmaster@palaceresorts.com).

Click [here](http://www.palaceresorts.com/d/palaceresorts/media/PDF/Palace_Privacy_Policy.pdf) to download Privacy Policy.
